=Afterlife of Love and Revenge= =Episode 2=
= الآخرة من الحب والانتقام = = الحلقة 2 =
Longyue,
لونجيوي ،
you weren't willing to marry me, were you?
لم تكن على استعداد للزواج مني أليس كذلك؟
They're all spreading the rumour
إنهم جميعًا ينشرون الشائعات
that I'm a woman of easy virtue.
أني امرأة ذات فضيلة سهلة.
Do you believe that?
هل تصدق ذلك؟
That's great.
ذلك رائع.
They all said that I'm a pervert.
قالوا جميعًا إنني منحرف.
We're
كانوا
a match made in heaven.
مباراة في السماء.
(Looking at him now,)
(أنظر إليه الآن)
(my husband is quite handsome.)
(زوجي وسيم جدا.)
(I shall not hesitate.)
(لن أتردد).
Longyue, are you awake?
لونجيوي ، هل أنت مستيقظ؟
I'm going back.
سأعود.
Longyue, I'm afraid you're not used to doing chores.
Longyue ، أخشى أنك لست معتادًا على القيام بالأعمال المنزلية.
So, I've asked a servant to stay here.
لذا طلبت من خادمة أن تبقى هنا.
(Pei Jinheng) Longyue,
(باي جينهينج) لونجيوي ،
don't marry him.
(Pei Jinheng) لا تتزوج منه.
(Pei Jinheng) Come with me.
(باي جينهينج) تعال معي.
Look at you.
انظر لحالك.
It seems like
انها تبدو مثل
the rumour about you being a woman of easy virtue
الإشاعة عن كونك امرأة ذات فضيلة سهلة
is real!
انه حقيقي!
No.
رقم.
On the first day of your marriage,
في اليوم الأول من زواجك ،
(Mother in law) you've brought the adulterer home.
(حماتك) لقد أحضرت الزاني إلى المنزل.
No, I...
لا ، أنا ...
Shut up!
اسكت!
(Constable Pang) Why did I have
(كونستابل بانغ) لماذا فعلت
a shameless daughter like you?
ابنة وقحة مثلك؟
From now on,
من الان فصاعدا،
you're no longer a part of Pang family.
لم تعد جزءًا من عائلة بانغ.
(It seems like Shuangyue)
(يبدو مثل Shuangyue)
(kept Pei Jinheng here as a trap)
(أبقي Pei Jinheng هنا كمصيدة)
(in the previous life.)
(في الحياة السابقة).
This man is useless
هذا الرجل عديم الفائدة
and broke.
وكسر.
Once I've thought of how you need to suffer
بمجرد أن فكرت في كيفية احتياجك للمعاناة
with a loser like him for the rest of your life,
مع خاسر مثله لبقية حياتك ،
I really think it's unfair for you.
أعتقد حقًا أنه غير عادل بالنسبة لك.
How great would it be if I can get married to Jinheng.
كم سيكون رائعًا إذا كان بإمكاني الزواج من Jinheng.
Longyue,
لونجيوي ،
I'll give you a surprise.
سأعطيك مفاجأة.
Come with me quickly.
تعال معي بسرعة.
Jinheng is inside the room.
جينهينج داخل الغرفة.
Longyue!
لونجيوي!
Someone!
شخصا ما!
It's on fire!
انها على النار!
Longyue!
لونجيوي!
There's someone in there! Save her!
هناك شخص ما هناك!  أنقذها!
Shuangyue?
Shuangyue؟
You're shameless.
أنت وقح.
You're not my daughter!
أنت لست ابنتي!
Father.
أب.
Father, listen to my explanation.
أبي ، استمع إلى شرحي.
It's Longyue.
إنها Longyue.
She wanted to have an affair with Pei Jinheng
أرادت أن تقيم علاقة غرامية مع Pei Jinheng
and she locked me in the woodshed.
وحبستني في مخزن الحطب.
You know that
هل تعلم أن
Longyue and Pei Jinheng were childhood sweethearts.
كان Longyue و Pei Jinheng أحباء الطفولة.
They've been in love.
لقد كانوا في حالة حب.
Say something.
قل شيئا.
I...
أنا...
I'm indeed here to meet Longyue.
أنا هنا بالفعل لمقابلة لونجيوي.
Longyue,
لونجيوي ،
you're shameless.
أنت وقح.
It's obvious that they're having an affair,
من الواضح أنهما على علاقة غرامية ،
why are you scolding me?
لماذا توبيخني
You...
أنت...
Father,
أب،
Longyue was with me all the time.
كان لونجي معي طوال الوقت.
She didn't go to the woodshed.
لم تذهب إلى مخزن الحطب.
Father, did you hear that? It's obviously...
أبي ، هل سمعت ذلك؟  أنه من الواضح أنه...
Shut up!
اسكت!
If your sister didn't find out about
إذا لم تكتشف أختك
how you're having an affair,
كيف لديك علاقة غرامية ،
I wouldn't have let you marry him.
لم أكن لأدعك تتزوجه.
Now, even your sister has been
الآن ، حتى أختك كانت كذلك
influenced by you.
تأثرت بك.
Constable Pang.
كونستابل بانغ.
This is your family matter.
هذه مسألة عائلتك.
Please handle it back home.
يرجى التعامل معها في المنزل.
Li Qingmu!
لي تشينغمو!
How dare you!
كيف تجرؤ!
Since you don't want to admit Longyue,
بما أنك لا تريد الاعتراف بـ Longyue ،
she'll no longer be your daughter.
لن تكون ابنتك بعد الآن.
She'll be Li Qingmu's wife.
ستكون زوجة لي تشينغمو.
No one in the world can bully my wife.
لا أحد في العالم يستطيع أن يتنمر على زوجتي.
Not even
ليس حتى
you.
أنت.
♪You're the fated love coming from the immortal world♪
أنت الحب المقدّر الآتي من العالم الخالد
♪You tie the red strings on the tips of my fingers♪
♪ تقوم بربط الخيوط الحمراء على أطراف أصابعي ♪
♪My heart won't change even if time passes♪
♪ قلبي لن يتغير حتى لو مر الوقت
♪I'll wait for the love in the old place as promised♪
♪ سأنتظر الحب في المكان القديم كما وعدت ♪